omgchrome.com 2019-05-09

# Privacy Policy - OMG! Chrome!

## **Privacy Policy for omgchrome.com**

The privacy of readers – regular, casual or one off – here at _OMG! Chrome!_ is important.

We recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information is received and collected when you use and visit us at omgubuntu.co.uk and how we safeguard your information. We **_never_** sell your personal information to third parties.

### Log Files

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

### Cookies & Web Beacons

Cookies are used on this site to store information for analytics, social interaction, advertisements, and certain features used on individual articles (e.g., polls).

Amongst the services that use cookies on this site are:

  * Google Analytics and [Gaug.es](http://gaug.es/) for analytics
  * BuySellAds and Google AdSense for advertisements
  * Twitter, Facebook, and Google+ for social interaction
  * Disqus for commenting
  * PollDaddy for polls and surveys

Some  advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geo-targeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs.
